Fadel Muhammad

Back-End Developer

About

I am learning about programing more than 2 years. I am a fast learner and, I am ready for learn about new programing language on my current company I am developing 2 project using Laravel with good team and I provide every datas on database SQL/Non-SQL for mobile developer (API) and fixing some bug using Node.Js, Go, Php on my freelancing job.

Education

Universitas Bina Sarana Informatika (GPA 3.76) Associate of Computer - System Information, 2017 - 2020

Experiences

PT Rekayasa Aplikasi Digital

Oct 2020 - Dec 2021

Full-Stack Developer

- Lead Of Project Sekolahdigi & Bantubeli
- Developing Apps & Website Bantubeli using Laravel
- Developing Apps & Website Sekolahdigi using Laravel
- Coordinating across teams (Mobile and Front-End)
- Integration Payment Gateway
- Integration Shipping Delivery Service on Bantubeli
- Helping team on fixing some bugs

PT Sahabat Sejahtera

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020

Full-Stack Developer

- Developing website catalog using Codelgniter
- Management all product on website

LSP Nusantara Jakarta

Jul 2017 - Dec 2019

IT Support

- Mantainance Computer,
- Fixing Connection Internet
- Creating Network Topology
- Installing some program when needed

Skills

HTML/CSS

Express Js

Laravel

Codelgniter

Go

SQL (Oracle, MySQL)

Non-SQL (Firebase)

Have knowledge about creating

REST API

Have knowledge data structures

Familiar using Git

Languages

English: Written.

Indonesia: Spoken, Written.

Contact

Email: fadel.mm01@gmail.com

Linkedin: Fadel Muhammad

Telp: 081290669170 Github: sipadl Instagram: si.padl